Guide to the Norman Hurd Ricker Papers, 1916-1978 MS 398
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Artifacts and Ephemera, 237821
  - Photograph album marked, "West Texas.", 237829 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Photograph album marked, Seismic Exploration, 237828 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Photograph album marked, Plunger Lift, 237827 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Photograph album marked, The Rice Institute, 237826 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Unmarked photograph album containing [Rice?] institute shots., 237825 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Notebook including typewritten speech and sequence of graphs and charts, corresponding to numbered slides. Entitled, Slides: Notes and Formulae., 237824 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Arrangement note
    This item [Notebook including typewritten speech, etc.] was formerly in box 24. Box 24 has been removed and the items have been incorporated into box 23 or deaccessioned.
  - Small plastic Kodak box containing photographic slides of graphs and of McDonald Observatory, Mt. Locke, Texas., 237823 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Arrangement
    This item [Small plastic Kodak box, etc.] was formerly in box 24. Box 24 has been removed and the items have been incorporated into box 23 or deaccessioned.
  - Cardboard box containing glass slides in metal mounts. Marked, Early days at Rice. World War I Air Service Photos. Florence Ricker's Wedding., circa 1920s, undated; 237822 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    This item [Cardboard box containing glass slides, etc.] was formerly in box 24. Box 24 has been removed and the items have been incorporated into box 23 or deaccessioned.